Guide to the Cornell Oral History Program records, 1964-1974.
Cornell Oral History Program records, 1964-1974
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Oral History Program records, 1964-1974.
13-6-1747
Cornell University.Program in Oral History.
5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, financial records, travel records, seminars, talks, papers, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence and printed material relating to the formation of the Oral History Association and the conduct of oral history colloquia; correspondence related to the Oral History Program at Cornell University, directed by Gould P. Colman; projects undertaken or proposed; financial records; payrolls; travel records; records relating to the Sarah Diamant film project; and seminars, talks, and papers on oral history by Colman.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence and printed material relating to the formation of the Oral History Association and the conduct of oral history colloquia; correspondence related to the Oral History Program at Cornell University, directed by Gould P. Colman; projects undertaken or proposed; financial records; payrolls; travel records; records relating to the Sarah Diamant film project; and seminars, talks, and papers on oral history by Colman.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Colman, Gould P., 1926-; Diamant, Sarah.; Oral History Association.
Subjects:
Oral history.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also Cornell University. Oral History Program records, #13-6-1394.
CONTAINER LIST
- Oral History Colloquium 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1968 Colloquium, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Oral History Colloquium 1972, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Oral History Colloquium 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Colloquium - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 4th Colloq., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Oral History Colloquium, 1966-1967, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1st Colloq. on Oral History, ca. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Demonstration Interviews (Cooperstown), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Immigration, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Application for Public Health Service Grant or Award, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Publication 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- "Put the Cradle in Motion: ...", 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Jr High Pilot Project, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Debye Int., ca. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cyrus Ching, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Scala Project, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Afro-American Asso, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- P W G Interview, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Brochure (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Immigration, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Rochester Study, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Ed Keuchel, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dolores Greenberg, College of Home Economics, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Univ. Oral History Center, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- George Jr. Republic (Jack Holl), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Secondary Education, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Xerox, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NFO, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- ILR, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Ithaca Festival, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- McCarthy, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- [Interview with Prof. Nimmer], n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Suggestion, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Oral History & the Public Schools, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Challenge to Gov., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Nantucket HABS, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Student Activism, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- NLRB, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Woopsie File, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Ag History Membership, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- School of the Ozarks, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- ILR Local Unions, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Goals & Guidelines Statement, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1961-June 30, 1967 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, July 1, 1967-Dec. 30, 1970 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, Jan. 1, 1971-June 30, 1972 (Box 5)
- Financial records, payroll, expense sheets, travel records, ca. 1961-1965, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
- Gould Colman project files (partial), ca. 1965-1972 (Box 5)
- Financial records, payroll, expense sheets, travel records, 1965-1971 (Box 6)
- Records relating to Sarah Diamant film project and $2000 received from ILR (Box 6)
- Additional records (Box 7)
- William Cutler files and correspondence (Box 7)
  Correspondents include Katherine Taylor, Gould Colman, William Gragg, others.
- Card index files (Box 8-15)